<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Expandable List View Three</string>

    <string-array name="header_string">
        <item> AGP </item>
        <item> BIOS </item>
        <item> CPU  </item>
        <item> DDR </item>
        <item> DIMM </item>
        <item> DRAM </item>
        <item> DVI </item>
        <item> ECC </item>
        <item> GPU </item>
        <item> HDD </item>
        <item> HDTV </item>
        <item> IDE </item>
        <item> ISA </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="child_string">
        <item>
            Accelerated Graphics Port.
            A type of video interface introduced in 1996 as an improvement to PCI.
            It has now been largely replaced by PCI-e.
        </item>
        <item>
            Basic Input-Output Service.
            This information is stored on a chip commonly referred to as the CMOS chip\,
            which really isn\'t a CMOS chip at all.
        </item>
        <item>
            Compact Disc.
            A type of optical media\,
            so called because it uses light to read the data stored on the disk.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Central Processing Unit\, Microprocessor\, or simply Processor.
        </item>
        <item>
            Double Data Rate.
            A type of memory that sends and receives data twice every clock cycle\,
            and therefore is capable of twice the data transfer rate of standard SDRAM.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dual In-Line Memory Module.
            A type of memory chip that uses a 64-bit bus, as compared to SIMM chips\,
            which used a 32-bit bus.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dynamic Random Access Memory.
            A type of RAM that stores each bit of data on separate capacitors.
        </item>
        <item>
            Digital Video.
            A protocol for the storage and transfer of audio-visual information\,
            often used to transfer information from a camcorder to a computer\,
            usually over a Firewire interface.
        </item>
        <item>
            Digital Video Interface.
            A type of digital video interface that can be used by computers and other video devices.
            It was an improvement over VGA\, but is starting to be obsolesced by HDMI.
        </item>
        <item>
            Error Correction Code.
            ECC Memory uses a parity bit to insure that data has been transmitted correctly.
            It is both slower and more expensive than non-ECC memory\, but it\'s more reliable
        </item>
        <item>
            Graphics Processing Unit.
            The chip on a video card that processes graphics and video.
            Sometimes integrated on the motherboard\, and sometimes on the CPU itself.
        </item>
        <item>
            Hard Disk Drive.
            An array of magnetic disks that store data until it is intentionally deleted by the user\,
            the system, or a program.
        </item>
        <item>
            High-Definition Television.
            The over-the-air television standard that replaced NTSC in the United States.
            Tuners are available that allow HDTV signals to be captured and processed on a computer\,
            enabling the user to watch TV on his or her computer.
        </item>
        <item>
            Integrated Device Electronics. See EIDE above.
        </item>
        <item>
            Industry Standard Architecture.
            An obsolete expansion interface\,
            which began to be replaced by PCI and AGP in the mid-1990\'s.
        </item>


    </string-array>




</resources>
